toponereport.com 2016-04-13

# Top One Report » Privacy

##  [ Privacy ](http://www.toponereport.com/privacy/ "Permanent Link to Privacy")

** Privacy Policy For: TopOneReport.com**

****  
Flying Monkey Media, Inc. understands that you may have concerns about safeguarding your privacy on-line. The Privacy Statement that follows explains our views and practices concerning privacy, and how they may pertain to you as you make full use of our many offerings. This statement discloses the privacy practices for all Flying Monkey Media, Inc. websites including the website you are currently visiting where you are reading this Privacy Policy.

**Article 1. Collection of Personal Information from Site Visitors**

Flying Monkey Media, Inc. automatically collects and/or tracks (1) the home server domain names, IP address, e-mail addresses, type of client computer, and type of Web browser of visitors to Flying Monkey Media, Inc’s Web site, (2) the e-mail addresses of visitors that communicate with Flying Monkey Media, Inc. via e-mail, (3) information such as personal, financial or demographic information, knowingly provided by the visitor in on-line forms, registration forms, surveys, and sweepstakes entries, and (4) information, either in the aggregate or user specific, on what pages visitors access.

Flying Monkey Media, Inc. places Internet cookies on visitors’ hard drives. We use cookies to deliver information and content specific to your interests, and to save your password so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. Internet cookies save the visitor’s name, password, user-name, screen preferences, the pages of the Flying Monkey Media, Inc’s Web site viewed by the visitor, and the advertisements viewed or clicked by the visitor. When the visitor revisits the Flying Monkey Media, Inc’s Web site, Flying Monkey Media, Inc. will recognize the visitor by the Internet cookie and customize the visitor’s experience accordingly. Internet cookies are stored on the visitor’s hard drive and are not stored, in any form, by Flying Monkey Media, Inc.. Visitors may decline the Internet cookie by using the appropriate feature of their Web browser software, if available.

**Article 2. Use of Personal Data Collected**

Personal data collected by Flying Monkey Media, Inc. will be used by Flying Monkey Media, Inc. for editorial and feedback purposes, for marketing and promotional purposes, for a statistical analysis of users’ behavior, for future product development, for content improvement, to inform advertisers as to how many visitors have seen or clicked their advertisements, and to customize content and layout of Flying Monkey Media, Inc’s site. Names, postal and e-mail addresses, and phone numbers collected may be added to Flying Monkey Media, Inc’s databases and used for future e-mails, calls and mailings regarding site updates, new products and services, upcoming events, and status of orders placed online. Financial information collected may be used to check the user’s qualifications for registration, to bill the user for products and services, to notify the user in the event of sweepstakes winnings, and to notify the relevant taxing and regulatory authorities regarding payments or prizes.

Demographic and profile data collected is used to tailor the visitor’s experience at our site, enabling us to present content we think they might be interested in. We use customer contact information to send the user information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. The customer’s contact information is also used to contact him or her in the event of a sweepstakes winning, and to notify the relevant taxing and regulatory authorities regarding payments or prizes.

**Article 3. Disclosure of Personal Data to Third Parties**

Flying Monkey Media, Inc. reserves the right to share, rent, sell, or otherwise disclose data it collects on Flying Monkey Media, Inc’s Web site to third parties. Any third party to which Flying Monkey Media, Inc. shares, rents, sells, or otherwise discloses personal data will be carefully pre-screened by Flying Monkey Media, Inc., determined by Flying Monkey Media, Inc. to be reputable, and will use the personal data for marketing products and services which Flying Monkey Media, Inc. determines, in its sole judgment, that visitors might find of interest. Flying Monkey Media, Inc. will disclose to third parties information knowingly and voluntarily disclosed by visitors, or information in aggregate form.

Through the use of third party cookies, an advertiser will be electronically notified when visitors view or click on its advertisements. This site contains links to other sites and Flying Monkey Media, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites.

**Article 4. Opt-Out Right**

We allow users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we voluntary request information about the visitor. This site also allows users to remove their information from our database. If a user removes his or her information from the Flying Monkey Media, Inc. database it will no longer be used by Flying Monkey Media, Inc. for secondary purposes, disclosed to third parties, or used by Flying Monkey Media, Inc. or third parties to send promotional correspondences to the visitor. Users can remove their information by writing to us via postal mail at the address below, or by sending an email requesting removal to [insert e-mail for remove].

Visitors may opt out of having their personal information collected by Flying Monkey Media, Inc., by contacting Flying Monkey Media, Inc. via postal mail to the address below, or via e-mail to support@infomediainc.com.

**Article 5. Access to and Ability to Correct Personal Data**

Upon request via postal mail or e-mail, Flying Monkey Media, Inc. will provide to visitors a summary of any personal information retained by Flying Monkey Media, Inc. regarding the visitor. Flying Monkey Media, Inc. will only send personal records to the e-mail address on file for the visitor name associated with it. Visitors may modify, correct, change, or update their personal record or cause their personal record to be removed from Flying Monkey Media, Inc’s database. Visitors may change or modify information previously provided by by contacting Flying Monkey Media, Inc. via postal mail to the address below, or via e-mail to support@infomediainc.com.

**Article 6. Collection of Personal Data from Children**

The information and services provided at Flying Monkey Media, Inc.’s web site by Flying Monkey Media, Inc., its affiliates, sponsors, and advertisers are not intended to be viewed by children under 13 years of age. All sweepstakes offered at Flying Monkey Media, Inc. are open to United States residents 18 years or older only. Flying Monkey Media, Inc. will not knowingly permit a child to participate in a game, offering of a prize, or another activity. If a child wins a sweepstakes, that child’s entry will be voided, and another winner will be drawn.

Concerning visitors to its site that it knows are children under 13 years of age, Flying Monkey Media, Inc. maintains the following policies:

– Flying Monkey Media, Inc. will not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 years of age without prior parental consent, which will include an opportunity for the parent to prevent use of the information and participation in the activity. Without prior parental consent, on-line information will only be used to respond directly to the child’s request and will not be used for other purposes without prior parental consent.

– In the event a child submits information to the Flying Monkey Media, Inc. Web site, the child must provide an e-mail address for the child’s parent or guardian. Thereafter, Flying Monkey Media, Inc. will send an e-mail to the parent or guardian alerting them to the child’s registration and providing instructions on how the parent can provide consent for the child to view the contents of Flying Monkey Media, Inc., or how the parent could view or delete the child’s registration, if so desired.

– Flying Monkey Media, Inc. will not knowingly distribute to third parties any personally identifiable offline contact information concerning children under 13 years of age without prior parental consent.

– No information collected from children is knowingly used for any marketing or promotional purposes whatsoever, either inside or outside Flying Monkey Media, Inc..

Article 7. Flying Monkey Media, Inc’s Right to Contact User

Flying Monkey Media, Inc. reserves the right to contact site visitors regarding account status and changes to subscriber agreements, privacy policy, or any other policies or agreements relevant to site visitors.

Article 8. Flying Monkey Media, Inc’s Right to Change Privacy Policy

Flying Monkey Media, Inc. reserves the right to change this policy at any time by notifying visitors of the existence and location of the new or revised privacy policy.

Contacting Flying Monkey Media, Inc.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact:

Flying Monkey Media, Inc.  
1151 Eagle Dr Ste 325  
Loveland, CO 80537  
[Support Desk](http://support.infomediainc.com/).
